Mateo Rodriguez

Phone: (970) 978-8409 | Email: mateo.rodriguez85@gmail.com | Location: Denver, CO

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mateo-rodriguez-86aba5aa/
Portfolio: https://mateo-rodriguez-react-portfolio.netlify.app/

Portiono. <u>Inteps.//mateo-rounguez-react-portiono.netin</u>

GitHub: https://github.com/AztekAsylum

Creative Front End Developer with a background in graphic design and a specialization in clean front-end design. Experience honed in graphic design, photography, and videography facilitates the creation of unique content for promotional purposes and engagement. Through the creative process, adaptation with a strong work ethic is manifested, and the enjoyment of collaborating with others is a constant along the journey.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, GIT, Web APIs, Third-Party APIs, Server-Side APIs, Node.js, Videography, Adobe Creative Suite, MongoDB, Photography, Object-Oriented Programming (OOP), GraphQL, Insomnia, Express.js, Bootstrap, SQL, Handlebars, Object-Relational Mapping, Model-View-Controller (MVC) Computer Science for JavaScript, No SQL, Progressive Web Applications (PWA), MERN, & State.

PROJECTS

Hack The Planet | Deployed Project: https://devshacktheplanet-44c29a23ae44.herokuapp.com/ Repo: https://github.com/AztekAsylum/hack_the_planet

- Summary: full-stack e-commerce website for tech enthusiasts offering the latest and greatest in hardware with a full checkout functionality through stripe.
- Role: Front-end design and functionality
- Technologies: VS Code, GitHub, GraphQL, Node.js, MongoDB, Heroku, JWT, React, Bootstrap, CSS and Stripe

EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer, Oct 2019 - PRESENT Freelance Denver,CO

Executed screen printed graphics for t-shirts. Flier design for promotional music and art in a timely manner for clients. Designed & embroidered hats & t-shirts. Clothing product shots on models with attention to detail. Video work to promote clothing products using my creative thinking & organization.

Youth Program Coordinator & Art Show Curator D3 Arts

Jan 2021 - March 2022 Denver,CO

Generated in-house videos with collaboration with fellow teammates. Hand paint murals in the community. Set up & tear down art installations. Maintain and update D3 Arts website. Create content for social media pages. Work with at-risk youth to teach different disciplines of art tied into workshops. Design merch for fundraising for the non-profit.

Graphic Designer & Retail Sales Fice Gallery

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020 Denver,CO

Generated in-house designs for shirts, stickers, + more! Provided professional and friendly customer service. Restock inventory as needed. Maintain an accurate cash drawer. Maintain knowledge of a variety of streetwear and shoe products. Showcase the company in a positive light.

Graphic Designer May 2015 - Oct 2019
Jiberish Denver,CO

Generated in-house graphics for t-shirts, hoodies, hats, stickers + more! Helped model products to promote on instagram. Designed fliers and thank you product cards for customers/instagram. Helped pack and ship products to customers. Consistent check-ins with teammates to talk progress of projects. Meet consistent deadlines. Helped design and complete tech-packs for future lines with an eye for detail.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate | University of Denver Denver, CO | Aug 2023 - Nov 2023

Bachelor of Arts Graphic Design | University of Northern Colorado Greeley, CO | Aug 2011 - May 2014